<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Rateworld</string>
	<string name="near_by"><u>SHOW NEAR-BY EXCHANGE</u></string>
	<string name="near_by02">NEARBY EXCHANGES</string>
	<string name="about_us">About Us</string>
	<string name="instruction">Instructions</string>
	<string name="copyright">2015 Copyright Rateworld</string>
	<string name="right_reserved">All Right Reserved</string>
	<string name="map"><u>MAP</u></string>
	<string name="instructions"><u>INSTRUCTIONS</u></string>
	<string name="no_exchange">NO NEARBY\nEXCHANGE FOUND</string>
	<string name="about">Rateworld shows exchange rates of over 150 countries with easy and reliable 
	    interface.\n\nThe intuitive UI of Rateworld shows you all the information you need in one single 
	    screen.\n\n<u>FEATURES</u>\n\n1. Live currency exchange rates for more than 150 world currencies.
	    \n\n2. Currrency calculator to compare and calculate the curriencies.\n\n3. Show list of NEARBY 
	    money exchange centers within the range of 5 kms based on user current location.\n\n4. On-Map navigation between
	    the user\'s current location and money exchange center.\n\n5. Auto updation with 1 minute of time interval.
	    \n\n6. Daily NOTIFICATION of latest rates of selected currencies at 10 AM in the morning and 10 PM in the evening.
	    \n\n7. Offline mode to allow currency conversion without internet connection.\n\n8. Display amount up to 5 decimal places.
	    \n\n9. Add and compare too many currencies at the single time. </string>
	<string name="child_noti">Activate daily notification message of today\'s and previous day rates of selected currencies at 10 AM in the morning and 10 PM in the evening</string>
	<string name="instruction01">1. Tap on particular currency to set it as default.</string>
	<string name="instruction01_after"><u>After Tap</u></string>
	<string name="instruction02">2. Remove particular currency by sliding tab from right to left.</string>
	<string name="instruction03">3. User can add more currencies by clicking on \'plus\' button.</string>
	<string name="instruction03_after">On clicking, shows a popup with the list of currencies.</string>
	<string name="instruction04">4. By clicking on \'NEARBY EXCHANGE\' shows a popup with the list of all nearby exchange centers within a range of 5 Kms.</string>
	<string name="instruction04_after"><u>After click</u></string>	
	<string name="instruction04_last">Clicking on     shows on-map navigation between  users\'s current location and money exchange center.</string>
	
</resources>
